=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 23=
= الحلقة 23 =
(Women's restroom)
(دورة مياه النساء)
Weiyi,
وييي ،
are you okay?
انت بخير؟
If you want to cry,
إذا كنت تريد البكاء ،
I can find somewhere for you to hide.
يمكنني أن أجد مكانًا تختبئ فيه.
Don't stay quiet.
لا تسكت.
I'll buy some eggs now.
سأشتري بعض البيض الآن.
Let's smash the eggs against them.
دعونا نسحق البيض ضدهم.
Q.
س.
Look, our dewy foundation
انظروا ، مؤسستنا الندية
is not bad, right.
ليس سيئا ، أليس كذلك.
The banana skin hit right on my face.
ضرب جلد الموز على وجهي مباشرة.
But my foundation still looks perfect.
لكن مؤسستي لا تزال تبدو مثالية.
If this gets on the headline,
إذا كان هذا على العنوان الرئيسي ،
we can earn ourselves a free advertisement.
يمكننا كسب إعلان مجاني لأنفسنا.
Weiyi,
وييي ،
from today onwards, you are my goddess.
من اليوم فصاعدا ، أنت إلهة بلدي.
Sun Weiyi,
صن ويي ،
you just got promoted and this happened.
لقد تمت ترقيتك للتو وهذا ما حدث.
The damage caused to the company is beyond measure.
الضرر الذي لحق بالشركة لا يمكن قياسه.
Do you get it?
هل حصلت عليه؟
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
It has happened though.
لقد حدث ذلك رغم ذلك.
I'll do whatever I can to make up for it.
سأفعل كل ما بوسعي للتعويض عن ذلك.
Deal with it now.
تعامل معها الآن.
Miss Sun,
ملكة جمال صن ،
our boss said
قال رئيسنا
you can go in
يمكنك الدخول
whenever you visit.
كلما زرت.
No appointment is needed.
لا يوجد موعد مطلوب.
This way, please.
من هذا الاتجاه من فضلك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Are you really not attracted to Sun Weiyi?
هل أنت حقا لا تنجذب إلى Sun Weiyi؟
No.
رقم.
Why would I lie to you?
لماذا اكذب عليك؟
I still recall
ما زلت أتذكر
that you were so heartbroken
أنك كنت حزينًا جدًا
just because I gave her a small punishment.
فقط لأنني أعطيتها عقوبة صغيرة.
I was just acting.
كنت مجرد تمثيل.
Sun Weiyi is nothing but an ordinary girl.
صن ويي ليست سوى فتاة عادية.
I can find a lot of others like her on the street.
أستطيع أن أجد الكثير من الآخرين مثلها في الشارع.
I am seeking revenge.
أسعى للانتقام.
I'll let her depend on me first
سأتركها تعتمد علي أولاً
and then I'll dump her
وبعد ذلك سأتخلص منها
so she'll know how I felt
حتى تعرف كيف شعرت
when she dumped me.
عندما هجرتني.
Are you serious?
هل أنت جاد؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
I can have anything I want now,
يمكنني الحصول على أي شيء أريده الآن ،
including girls.
بما في ذلك الفتيات.
You are home, Weiyi.
أنت في المنزل ، وييي.
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
I'm so exhausted already
لقد استنفدت بالفعل
that I have no time to deal with you.
أنه ليس لدي وقت للتعامل معك.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Why didn't you ask for my help
لماذا لم تطلب مساعدتي
after such a serious matter happened today?
بعد أن حدث مثل هذا الأمر الخطير اليوم؟
Are you done with your acting?
هل انتهيت من تمثيلك؟
I feel tired by looking at it.
أشعر بالتعب من خلال النظر إليه.
What other tricks do you and your sister still have?
ما الحيل الأخرى التي لا تزال تملكها أنت وأختك؟
You'd better show me everything at once.
من الأفضل أن تريني كل شيء مرة واحدة.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I don't get it.
انا لم احصل عليها.
Well, you said
حسنا ، قلت
I'm just an ordinary girl
أنا مجرد فتاة عادية
and you can find a lot of others like me on the street.
ويمكنك أن تجد الكثير من الأشخاص مثلي في الشارع.
And you would
وستفعل
let me experience the feeling of being dumped.
اسمحوا لي أن أجرب الشعور بالإغراق.
You misunderstood me.
لقد أسأت فهمي.
I'm lying to Bai Lingfei.
أنا أكذب على باي لينجفي.
Do you know what she is doing behind you?
هل تعلم ماذا تفعل وراءك؟
Is it?
فعلا؟
What a great actor are you!
يا لك من ممثل عظيم!
Sun Weiyi,
صن ويي ،
you don't trust me.
أنت لا تثق بي.
Do you know how much I've done for you?
هل تعرف كم فعلت من أجلك؟
Don't you see it?
ألا تراها؟
I wanted to trust you too
اردت ان اثق بك ايضا
but I'm not deaf.
لكنني لست أصم.
All this while,
كل هذه الفترة،
you and your sister have been teaming up to get back at me
أنت وأختك تتعاونان معًا للعودة إلي
and fool me around.
وتخدعني.
Now that you are happy.
الآن بعد أن أصبحت سعيدا.
You've made it.
لقد نجحت.
Congratulations.
تهانينا.
After all, you don't trust me at all.
بعد كل شيء ، أنت لا تثق بي على الإطلاق.
How am I supposed to trust you?
كيف لي أن أثق بك؟
Bai Zeliu,
باي زيليو ،
it's over.
انتهى.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Are you breaking up with me?
هل تنفصل عني؟
I can't be in a relationship
لا أستطيع أن أكون في علاقة
that's full of plots.
هذا مليء بالمؤامرات.
Please,
لو سمحت،
spare me.
اعفنى.
♪My heart has skipped a beat♪
♪ قلبي تخطى خفقان ♪
♪Whose breathing is getting weaker?♪
لمن يضعف تنفسه؟
♪I don't wish to argue who's at fault♪
♪ لا أرغب في مناقشة من هو المخطئ
♪Who can understand my feelings?♪
♪ من يستطيع فهم مشاعري؟